<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Investcoex</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Investcoex</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Crypto app!</title>
      <link>/post/crypto-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/crypto-app/</guid>
      <description> Hello out there again. This is my second post here and I will be talking about the app I developed after submitting a work to SER - International Seminar on Statistics with R, hosted by UFF (Universidade Federal Fluminense).
The intention of this app is to provide an automatized solution for visualizing and modeling crypto data. The whole logic followed this path:
Create a logic to get data from here Get apps  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello world</title>
      <link>/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello world! Hello out there. This is Marcelo, a cryptocurrency ambassador, researcher, and modeler. Before that, I was nothing but:
an economist which had/wanted to learn a lot about stats and R language, a person who regrets to not have invested in cryptos the first time I’ve heard about it (who doesn’t?), a disciplined guy because of the way of programming, algorithms thinking style, and my need to finish my masters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic: the website designer for Hugo</title>
      <link>/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Academic makes it easy to create a beautiful website for free using Markdown. Customize anything on your site with widgets, themes, and language packs.
Follow our easy step by step guide to learn how to build your own free website with Academic. Check out the personal demo or the business demo of what you&amp;rsquo;ll get in less than 10 minutes.
 View the documentation Ask a question Request a feature or report a bug Updating?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>